Guide to the Cherry Tree Yearbook records, 1908-2005 RG0113
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs, 1998-2002; RG0113 Series 6; 3.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 2, Box 1, Box 7, Box 6, Box 5, Box 4)
  - Women's Basketball vs. UCLA, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Xavier, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Women's Crew, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Women's Cross-Country Team, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Women's Gymnastics, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Women's Soccer, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Women's Studies Program, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Women's Volleyball, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Women's Water Polo, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Wooden Teeth, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Word UP Bible Study, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - WRGW, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - WRGW Oktoberfest, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Photographs, 2002-2003; RG0113 Series 7; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  Photos from Cherry Tree - Aids walk, commencement, Colin Powell, community service, Kalb report, midnight madness, protest against war in Iraq, Spring Fling, women's lacrosse, 2002-2003.
  - AIDS Walk, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Colin Powell at Elliott School building dedication, 09/2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Community Service, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Demolition of old hospital, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Kalb Report - first anniversary of 9/11, 09/11/2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Midnight Madness, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - President Trachtenberg with Senator Bob Graham and Andrew Coumo, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Protest against war in Iraq, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Residence Hall Bistro, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Spring Fling, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cherry Tree and predecessor yearbooks, 1898-2009; RG0113 Series 8; 19.5 Linear Feet 13 document boxes; 22 Linear feet
  This series contains third, fourth, and additional copies of the yearbooks, which may be deaccessioned and gifted as needed.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Copies of the yearbooks for researcher use are stored in the Special Collections reading room (they are cataloged as LD 1947.C5 ref). This series of extra copies is not available for researcher use.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  The yearbooks have been scanned and are avaialble online through the Internet Archive.
  - Yearbooks 1898-1909 (missing 1900-1903) (Box 26)
  - Yearbooks 1910-1918 (missing 1915, 1919) (Box 27)
  - Yearbooks 1920-1928 (Box 28)
  - Yearbooks 1929-1937 (missing 1936) (Box 29)
  - Yearbooks 1938-1947 (Box 30)
  - Yearbooks 1948-1957 (Box 31)
  - Yearbooks 1958-1966 (Box 32)
  - Yearbooks 1967-1974 (Box 33)
  - Yearbooks 1975-1983 (Box 34)
  - Yearbooks 1984-1992 (missing 1989) (Box 35)
  - Yearbooks 1993-1999 (Box 36)
  - Yearbooks 2000-2004 (Box 37)
  - Yearbooks 2005-2009 (Box 38)
  - Yearbooks, 1899-1971 (Box 39)
    Scope and Contents
    Additional copies of Cherry Tree Yearbooks from the years:
    1904, 1913, 1922, 1926, 1949, 1952, 1971
    and copies of The Columbiad from the years:
    1891 and 1899
    and copies of The Mall from the years:
    1905 and 1906
- Photographs, 1990-1993; RG0113 Series 9; 1 Linear foot (Flat box 2, Flat box 1, Box 3)
  Photographs by Cherry Tree staff for 1990-1993 yearbooks
  Formerly Acc#204.
- Photographs, 1991-1993; RG0113 Series 10 (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 25)
  Formerly ACC#210